This takes us away from the complete alas consciousness.
But that's why we always try to motivate it.
We are going to eat, and it's a good food.
We are going to forget alas, so we must say this to him.
Even if he tries to say a hungry man.
But if he very up-off, if he very up-off-o-
of a heating, we forget our own.
So these permanent amendments are.
These people for being part of the show
as many philosophers can be shown to say,
in one's sensitive aspect of love,
love in the sense of the sex of heart.
This is given in memory, love.
So a guy's forgotten.
in the very moment of potential inequality.
So we cannot be absolutely
absolutely a land constant,
but we try to be a la culture.
So in terms of, we're trying to approximate
a life of paradise where everything is conscious
of a life.
Actually,
For this will be cornered, even these forms of prayer that we have,
from earth, in some ways.
They are closed to the forms of prayer in paradise.
There is prayer in paradise, sicorann teisso.
There is also prayer on earth.
And the prayer of the angel is also similar.
As it is a one-to-one correspondence.
We pray according to Quran, the angels ask for forgiveness for the sins of man. We ask for forgiveness for him in the next Allah.
The angels proclaim. They praise Allah. We pray for strength. We pray for strength. How? I don't know how, but there is a a a response.
And so just one little detail on surah 10 verse 10.
Don't forget the surah 10 verse 10.
The Quran speaks of existence of the taslim, the saying of salam in parada.
It talks of the takmi, the saying of a tambu de la.
A much very interesting is this, that in ten, ten, you understand, first ten.
This is a suggestion that all the last two, before this, salam,
I have lived more than half century and ten years added to half century.
I have read maybe thousands and thousands and dozens of books on how to pray a lot.
I have never found an instruction in this book
for how to play celeste.
Whether of the Hanafi, Mariki, Hanbali, or Shafi,
mother, or Disha, mother, I've not found anyone saying
that before you say, "As salamu alaikum,
"as salamu alaikum, you must say,
"an hambulillahi rampil alaikum."
And that's all.
Now, please do not misunderstand me,
I am not saying to you, and I am the last one to say to you.
You know my character by now, never believe in the post-image use.
I am not saying that before you say, "Acela mo a la echeleso," you must say, "I'll hunt you in the life of the land."
I will never say that. But I know of some people who say it.
And if I remember, I also say,
And the basis I think is in the first term of Surah 10, which says that the last Du'an,
the last prayer before this alarm is, that's in Holy Shashram, Wa'alaykum, the end of the
pasty, say, "Alhamdulillah, I love the alarm."
And there are various chapters of the Quran which end up with that place.
I'm not telling you what to do. I'm only saying what some people do, but I do sometimes when
I remember in what it is basis for saying a humble life of the element before you say
salamu alaykum, salamu alaykum, salamu alaykum. Maybe you can go to the Quran yourself and
find out the meaning of verse 10 in surah, 10. But I have not found any instruction book
I'm done.
It's very strange, but there are many people who do seba.
[ Inaudible ]
(speaking in foreign language)
[ Background noise ]
(chattering)
(speaking in foreign language)
[ Inaudible ]
>> I put you think then.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, it is in several in fact, I think it's at least three times.
>> Thank you.
[inaudible]
[ Laughter ]
[ Inaudible ]
to the last minor in the final prayer.
Just a few minutes.
And I think we have a sense of focus on our...
Who does that have to be the prayer of the Jesus?
But how many times do you want?
These people go out of this room.
All right.
[ Inaudible ]
(indistinct chatter)
(muffled speaking)
because it's not part of the survival.
It may not be.
So it's that after the season.
Yeah, but this is the kind of the point of Syria.
That's the Quran's name, just, even out of the flesh.
You can ask them.
That's the poem.
And I hope you can listen to this.
You know what?
What's the difference?
Mm?
How many times?
And even in my small country with the kids, we have a small country with them.
But we have a full-to-out of our institutions.
But not in the legislature.
Yeah.
I think I can.
We know our best.
No, not in the very only way.
I know our best.
We know our best.
(crowd chattering)
They were doing it.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
For me, the statistics are significant.
Being the lowest, you know, the highest point.
That's a phrase.
Oh my God.
(speaking in foreign language)
In the Salat itself.
[INTERPRETER]
How today? Because I have to educate.
None say that saying, "I'm here to be a part of this."
probably you know that in many practices in our countries, in South Asia, part of the Salab, it's been too soon to sit, it's been too soon to do, I mean, it's also a bit worse for that.
Many people do that between...
I'm not going to say that.
I'm going to say that. No, no, no.
I just want to do that.
Do that.
That would be a lot of food.
Do that in the middle of the sushi.
No, no, no.
I know some people who are not
before the...
before the sushi.
They have a very good perspective.
Oh, yeah.
They know people who are happy too.
Especially in the super prayer.
(indistinct chatter)
- Well, I do think I have something to say
because it's actually that one
I have a little bit of a...
- I have a good idea.
- Yeah, but the slope is most enough.
- Look, look, look.
Not the most enough.
It has to be half the slope.
It has to be the last thing.
(indistinct chatter)
It's not a great thing.
We do not do it again.
We are going to say it again.
It's a great thing.
You pretend that the final thing is the last thing to be said,
100 years ago.
When you say it's a long-awaited thing,
I'm like...
Some of you have been said.
the tradition of the Old Four, they have no idea what it is.
It's just the...
It's just the place where someone...
But it's not directed at the argument.
Maybe it does.
I mean...
You say the tradition is that there's the ages, the important angels, and others say,
well, it's the people that are on the side because of the...
the last thing is that you're going to come to a little now.
Right.
They're in their prayer.
No.
Yeah.
After that, the last thing was the ultimate.
But it could also be the ultimate.
But it's the highest form of the Lord, the Roman tomb.
The duh is between himself and God.
It's not to the Father, but nobody else.
Not the angels, not the other believers.
We can ask what the law is. But it seems to me that the law is so likely to be considered many ways apart of the new law.
The rest says the last thing they say is a hundred and a hundred and a hundred.
Seriously.
[ Inaudible ]
>> There's nothing wrong with that, I've been here for like,
you know, they're getting in the middle of the end.
[ Inaudible ]
I remember there was a lot of evidence that was, of course there was a, there was no firestorm, there was no effort.
>> [INAUDIBLE]
(indistinct chatter)
I want to offer you a little bit of a better thing.
We can go to the district.
I want to go to the district.
Because if you interpret the same thing,
you can say to anybody that's not allowed to be in the top party.
If you look at the district, you can go to the district.
I'll say the country is in the face.
I think a little bit about the district is in the top.
(indistinct chatter)
[ Inaudible ]
(crowd talking)
But those are human from there.
When you do not have to do that,
please give me a hand.
Please give me a hand.
I'm very, very happy.
I'm very happy.
But I'm very happy.
You know, we're very happy to get there.
We've got to do something.
Now, all thinking,
we start with that.
In 29,
(crowd talking)
(crowd chattering)
better farm farm.
(chattering)
[ Inaudible ]
(speaking in foreign language)
(indistinct chatter)
[ Inaudible ]
In heaven, who will give praise in God?
And who will be second to him for the night of heaven?
Help him be around for the bread.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(crowd chattering)
- Yeah, I know how they talk.
(speaking in foreign language)
Remember, you said not to eat your sister's anything.
Then you asked them to retire here.
Maybe you wanted to ask.
Oh, yeah?
There is a new button.
It was sitting closer to me.
Oh, see, the one is the suit.
Oh, why do we eat the food?
I can't have a clinic tonight.
I need to keep all the money.
I'm a victim of the relationship.
But yesterday I met somebody in the management.
He's a new piece.
He has!
I thought that there are companies.
I will have to get a photo.
I love the English.
Miss Mises you have decided to forget your photo.
I'm trying to take a photo.
I want to come to the police, sir.
Look at those curses.
Oh, yeah, the people.
Do you make this?
I can't.
Actually, I know.
Where are you, brother?
They went back to the police.
Oh, what are you talking about?
[ Inaudible ]
We are friends who are making some war.
We want to put out the movement.
So they don't have any--
I did.
Let's see if the patient is here.
But telephone is not the one who's here.
So I did try to be bored.
They will send me tea, but I'm going to take my mind to stay there.
It all depends on...
We're going to miss you here.
Are you going to suffer?
No, I'm kidding.
You're going to die, baby.
You're going to die?
I don't know.
You know when...
You know when I don't know when I'm...
You know, it's not supposed to be always...
And then maybe...
Because we give it ticket to go back. I might use it to go to a mission.
My husband, who goes to a mission. He takes it home. Take a plant in town.
[ Inaudible ]
Oh, there's a guy in this one. That's the guy. For somebody from Michigan.
From Michigan? Yeah.
Yeah. And I might say, no. Oh.
We are the store. You see there now?
He had a fight with Wally or something.
And then he played? Yeah.
Which is good.
What did he do at home? Yeah.
I thought you were not coming.
Yeah, the other part was well, not well, David.
Who?
You start them?
Yeah.
If you hit your stairs.
Which was tough?
Yeah, but what problem did you have to do with that time in here?
Well, I think you went home and you found the stuff I had talking with his wife or something.
I was about the one who stood here again, never would have said more so I said "I'm gonna hear you"
What's the last one?
No, the root means the meter doesn't come either.
[laughs]
You did the function of testing.
[inaudible]
Do you remember?
The old little black man.
Oh, that was that one.
I'm going to go with this.
He was a young guy.
He was a good boy.
I remember I never seen him in the ground.
I never talked to him.
You're just as rude. You're not as rude.
You're not as rude.
I want to be as rude again.
I can't take anything to the city.
Well, I just gained some weight, I'm already on your way.
This is perfect now.
I did very good this way.
I'll give you 100 feet of weight.
You know, I want to do this weight for one simple reason.
Because I followed my suits, my wooden suits are tight.
You're very low.
And I've used them for a million, a million stores.
And you don't want to build, you make a new one.
I don't want to buy new one.
How can you gain some weight?
You've gained some weight?
Yes.
About 10 pounds?
Yeah.
I'm not good.
You remember that?
Yeah.
I listened to it.
When you were in a dump.
So now you're going to try to sweat it out in this.
Oh, okay.
I don't know.
You have to open my eyes.
This is really hard.
It's a good thing to just.
because they're just very good exercises for the hard side.
But if your heart is already bad, you may have trouble.
Just walk, I guess.
Walk with the best.
I think how young people can tell you that Richard Harroff,
one of the most prominent scholars of the home come,
will open a urtic.
(chatter)
[ Inaudible ]
We're famous for real things.
There's other things.
Oh, John, it doesn't work.
Doesn't taste very much.
You bad your bad.
God wants you to go.
You're done.
I'd be 36 next year or so.
It was very, he wrote several dictionaries
and grammars of colloquial.
Maybe a noun.
the gold horse before he ends up stronger. The Arabianist. Because this development of
financial Arabic in the long run is a fight against the just Arab big, which is in the long run, the fight against the man. In the western of the winter it's been trying to develop the man Arab big to be like latin, became friend, you know, the father of the American.
And the French did it.
But I mean it happens naturally anyway.
They're merely reporting what's happened.
Yeah, but in Seoul, formalizing it,
there is 50 generalizes.
Which is not very good.
It is cut out of some each other.
The Egyptian, the CIA,
what is it?
The
foreign people, or
it's a form of the bigger mission.
Yeah, but they do it themselves. I mean Arabs do their own grammar.
Let this do it.
But no grammar written in the whole film, I would just ever find it.
Just some.
Yeah, there are.
But this hero has been one way to lose his scheme.
He wasn't English.
He studied the language from the outside.
Collected the data and wrote a grammar.
No, it was a grammar for non-Arab speakers, not for Arab speakers.
It was a, it was a, it was a, a grind.
It just kicked your grandma.
(crowd chattering)
And of course they're very important.
They'll put on modern, so-called modern.
Then they have the modern standards, you know,
and mix them with all people.
(crowd chattering)
- More for it.
- Yeah, yeah, and let me get in there
because I move my car and he's trying to get on.
We have to develop a little bit of development.
I know some millionaires.
Yeah.
Well, pretty fantastic.
Oh, yeah.
Translated by one.
All right.
So, you know, they could people who can read it,
or read it.
Very very very.
Uh, people who can say people who say people who are still out of contact.
Yeah.
That's a different matter.
We need to look at the translate, even English,
in the croquo language because it doesn't fit in the grammatical rules.
Every language has grammatical rules. You explain that you have a standardizing rule.
So you have a standardizing form. That's the accepted form. What I'm saying is you can say they're a colloquial
that I see in pigeon languages. When you talk about a grammar, it doesn't necessarily mean
He means correct or incorrect.
You're only talking about the structure of the language.
So you can have colloquial.
We can talk about the grammar of colloquial Arabic.
And it makes you may say, well, this grammar is in the person.
When you adopt a standard, then you can talk about something
being incorrect, but it's easier for the standard.
But if you see, beauty is scripted.
And you can speak about the grammar of the structure
of colloquial language.
[INAUDIBLE]
But there is no one.
Who happened to write?
But here's the story.
People might write them in the fire.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
The writing is the writing.
But even though--
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
--the rules that they need to get in mind,
you have to make up the new rules.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
Yeah, you can say, I want to go there.
You write it.
>> You do it.
>> It doesn't sound as if you're in the right place.
>> So, although this spelling is different, yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, what is the word?
>> That's what it says.
>> So, for example, colloquial language is used as many
as you want to go on.
>> It's not word in the classical language.
And then you'll work the closely with colloquial language.
>> It's a short form.
>> Something's got to all more.
>> It's right.
>> Yeah.
>> But you can write it down.
So, you can see.
It's only when you say, "This is his dad."
But you go to the correct branch.
I'm sorry.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I used to have my father.
He started to read the rhyme.
He had problems with you.
You read the rhyme.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
He only read the rhyme too.
He was told, "Hello, Vittarari, I don't know."
I started when all these conversations increased by the truth of the new Mr. Mohor, so I tell you, he did the things. My heart is just no, you cannot write it. It says you.